tollbrothers.com 2019-05-22

# Toll Brothers - Privacy Policy

* * *

Effective Date: May 3, 2018

Revised: August 6, 2018

At Toll Brothers, we understand that the privacy of the information provided to us is very important to you. By using this website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not use the website. Toll Brothers reserves the right, in our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time, without prior notice to you. We urge you to review this Privacy Policy frequently for changes. Your continued use of the website means that you accept those changes.

**Information We Collect, How it is Collected, and How it is Used**

We collect personally identifiable information (such as name, street address, email address and phone number) which you have voluntarily submitted to us through features of the website such as contact forms. We may use your personal information to respond to your inquiries and to provide you the most helpful and targeted products and services. Information on our products and services may be sent to you via the mail, email or text message. To better meet your needs, we may supplement the information we collect with data obtained from third parties for the same purposes.

We also automatically log your IP address in order to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our website and track usage statistics. Your IP address may vary each time you visit, or it may be the same, depending on your internet provider. Either way, it would be extremely difficult for us to identify you through your IP address, and we make no attempt to do so. If you reached our site by clicking on a link or advertisement on another site, then we also log that information. This helps us maximize our internet exposure, and it helps us understand our users' interests. All of this information is collected and used only in the aggregate; that is, it is entered into our database, where we can use it to generate overall reports on our visitors, but not individual reports that identify you personally.

We also place a small text file known as a "cookie" on your computer's hard drive. A cookie may contain information that allows us to track your path through our website and to determine whether you have visited us before. Unless you register with us, however, a cookie contains no information that would allow us to identify you. We use cookies to help us understand how visitors use our site, and to help us to improve our site. You may refuse to accept a cookie from us by following the procedures specific to your web browser. Although you may do so, you may find that your browser reacts strangely when visiting not only our website, but other websites as well. Since cookies don't provide us with any information from which we can identify you, we suggest you allow us to place one on your computer.

We may use web beacons on our site or other sites and may permit third parties to place them on our site to monitor the effectiveness of advertising or for other legitimate purposes. A web beacon, also known as a "web bug," is a small, graphic image on a webpage, web-based document or in an e-mail message that is designed to allow the site owner or a third party to monitor who is visiting a site. Web beacons are often invisible to the user because they are typically very small (only 1-by-1 pixel) and the same color as the background of the webpage, document or e-mail message. Web beacons are represented as HTML IMG tags in the webpage; users can click on "view profiles" of the webpage to see whether the page is using a web beacon. Web beacons collect the IP address of the computer that the web beacon is sent to, the URL of the page the web beacon comes from and the time it was viewed. Web beacons can also be linked to personal information. For example, advertising networks use web bugs to add information to a personal profile of what sites a person is visiting and to determine what banner ads to display based on the profile. Another use of web bugs is to provide an independent accounting of how many people have visited a particular website. Web bugs are also used to gather statistics about web browser usage at different places on the internet.

We may use third-party ad servers (or ad networks) to deliver ads to you on our behalf. These third-party ad servers may collect and use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our site in order to present advertisements that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice or to opt out of having this information used by third-party ad servers to provide targeted ads, please visit <https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

We also use Google Analytics, which uses first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and/or other first-party identifiers, and/or third-party cookies (such as Google Advertising cookies) or other third-party indentifiers to make advertising more engaging to our users. Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google that utilizes the data collected across multiple devices to track and examine the use of this website to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the date collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. The Google Analytics features we have implemented include Remarketing with Google Analytics; Google Display Network Impression Reporting; Google Signals; and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.

You may opt-out of Google Analytics tracking by visiting <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

We provide access to Google Maps. Information regarding users of Google Maps, including (but not limited to) identifiable information such as user name and your location may be gathered, used and retained by us. Personal information about you may also be gathered, used and processed by Google in accordance with Google's privacy policy. Google's privacy policy, including its' policy in connection with Google maps, is available at <https://www.google.com/privacy.html>.

**To Whom Information is Disclosed**

We may share your personally identifiable information, including your email address, with Toll Brothers' affiliated companies for the purpose of our affiliates informing you about their goods and services. We may also share your personally identifiable information i) with Toll Brothers' vendors as necessary to operate this website and fulfill your requests as submitted to this website, ii) as required by law, and iii) in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).

**Do Not Track**

Our websites do not support Do Not Track at this time. Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that you can set in your web browser to indicate that you do not want certain information about your webpage visits collected across websites when you have not interacted with that service on the page. For all the details, including how to turn on Do Not Track, visit [donottrack.us](http://donottrack.us/).

**Special Notice to California Residents**

Under California Law SB 27, California residents have the right to receive, once a year, information about third parties with whom we have shared information about you for their marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, and a description of the categories of personal information shared. To make such a request, please send an email to [TBMAILER@tollbrothers.com](mailto:TBMAILER@tollbrothers.com?subject=California%20Privacy%20Request) and please include the phrase "California Privacy Request" in the subject line, and provide us with your name, address and email address. We will respond to you within thirty days of receiving such a request.

**Unsubscribing from Emails**

If you are currently receiving emails from Toll Brothers and wish to be removed from our mailing list, [click here to remove yourself from our mailing list.](https://www.tollbrothers.com/my-favorites/unsubscribe)

**Cross-Border Transfer**

Your personally identifiable information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities and operations, and by providing any personally identifiable information to us, you consent to the transfer of such personally identifiable information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have different data protection rules from your country of residence.

**Children's Privacy**

The website is not intended for anyone under the age of thirteen. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of thirteen.

**Security**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially reasonable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Notification of Material Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This section identifies material changes to this Privacy Policy since the Effective Date.

(None at present.)

**Questions or Comments**

Toll Brothers welcomes questions and comments about this Privacy Policy. Questions or comments should be directed to the Chief Compliance Officer, who oversees Toll Brothers' compliance with privacy requirements at:

Chief Compliance Officer  
Toll Bros., Inc.  
250 Gibraltar Road  
Horsham, PA 19044
